<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>lhrb</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on lhrb</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 16:28:40 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Duality between data and code</title>
      <link>/post/dualityofcodeanddata/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 16:28:40 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/dualityofcodeanddata/</guid>
      <description>The first sentence on the Wikipedia page about &amp;ldquo;Code as data&amp;rdquo;:
 In computer science, the expressions code as data and data as code refer to the duality between code and data, that allows computers to treat instructions in a programming language as data handled by a running program. [0]
 I strongly associate the phrase &amp;ldquo;data as code&amp;rdquo; with LISP and I absolutely do love to speak about LISP but this time I will try to explore the other way around: &amp;ldquo;code as data&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Continuous Delivery for personal projects</title>
      <link>/post/simplebuildscript/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 19:17:23 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/simplebuildscript/</guid>
      <description>If you are like me, you build side projects from time to time. Some of them are application running on a server. This led me to the question what is a lightweight and simple way to deploy those application. Do I need to setup a full CI/CD pipeline? These are often heavy tools to run production grade software. Maybe a simple script is good enough for my use-case? After all, I&amp;rsquo;m most likely to abandon this project after a while.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 19:06:52 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m a software developer interested with everything that goes along with software. I enjoy learning about following topics most: Software Design, Programming Language Design, System Design, Lisp (Clojure in particular).
Here I learn to write and collect/share things I learned. I&amp;rsquo;m not a native speaker so pardon me for any mistakes I make.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
