<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on lhrb</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on lhrb</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2022 23:18:39 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Complex System</title>
      <link>/post/complex/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2022 23:18:39 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/complex/</guid>
      <description>What is a complex system? Just some thoughts:
 A single person can not understand a complex system. The same action may lead to different results.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pure functions? Effects?</title>
      <link>/post/purefunctions/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 13:56:06 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/purefunctions/</guid>
      <description>You already sold on the idea using and composing pure functions for &amp;ldquo;calculations&amp;rdquo; and pushing effects to the edge of your program. While you put a lot of effort in to internalize these ideas, some of your may never been co-workers exposed to these ideas. Leaving you with the task explaining it to them. You could either start talking about all these undeniable benefits or you could help your co-worker to build a mental model.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ignoramus</title>
      <link>/post/ignoramus/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 20:20:19 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/ignoramus/</guid>
      <description>In the book &amp;ldquo;Sapiens A Brief History of Humankind&amp;rdquo; Yuval Noah Harari describes that the scientific revolution happened because human were finally able to admit that &amp;lsquo;we do not know&amp;rsquo;.
While this probably holds true in broader terms. We still have to try hard not falling into the trap not questioning our self, thinking &amp;ldquo;I know&amp;rdquo;. Especially when we worked on something for a while and we are quit proud of it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Duality between data and code</title>
      <link>/post/dualityofcodeanddata/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 16:28:40 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/dualityofcodeanddata/</guid>
      <description>The first sentence on the Wikipedia page about &amp;ldquo;Code as data&amp;rdquo;:
 In computer science, the expressions code as data and data as code refer to the duality between code and data, that allows computers to treat instructions in a programming language as data handled by a running program. [0]
 I strongly associate the phrase &amp;ldquo;data as code&amp;rdquo; with LISP and I absolutely do love to speak about LISP but this time I will try to explore the other way around: &amp;ldquo;code as data&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Continuous Delivery for personal projects</title>
      <link>/post/simplebuildscript/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 19:17:23 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/simplebuildscript/</guid>
      <description>If you are like me, you build side projects from time to time. Some of them are application running on a server. This led me to the question what is a lightweight and simple way to deploy those application. Do I need to setup a full CI/CD pipeline? These are often heavy tools to run production grade software. Maybe a simple script is good enough for my use-case? After all, I&amp;rsquo;m most likely to abandon this project after a while.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
